doubledutch.me 2019-10-26

# Privacy Policy - DoubleDutch

Last Updated: March 31, 2018

This Privacy Policy is between the end user ("you", "your" or "End User") of the software application (“Licensed Application” as described in the EULA, <https://doubledutch.me/eula>, and/or website, <https://doubledutch.me/> (“Website”), and DoubleDutch, Inc., our subsidiaries DoubleDutch EMEA B.V. and DoubleDutch (Hong Kong) Limited, and our international subsidiaries (collectively “DoubleDutch”, “we”, “us” or “our”), a Processor, who collects and processes information on behalf of the App Partner (as described in the EULA). The App Partner is a third party beneficiary to this Privacy Policy, but may also have their own Privacy Policy linked in the Licensed Application. Upon your acceptance of this Privacy Policy, the App Partner will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce the terms of this Privacy Policy as a third party beneficiary of this Privacy Policy.

Please read this policy carefully, as it describes DoubleDutch’s use of your Personal Information (as defined in the EU Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC, or after May 25, 2018, the General Data Protection Regulation). By accessing and using the Website or Apps, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy, and are hereby consenting to our use of your Personal Information as set forth herein. You may withdraw consent at any time by contacting the App Partner or DoubleDutch. We may update this policy from time to time, and will announce this on our Website or in our event applications or web-based event registration portal ( **“Apps”** ). If any changes are material or apply to information we have already collected, we may provide additional notice and/or request additional consents as appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of the Apps or Website constitutes your acceptance of the updated terms. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Apps and Website.

**DoubleDutch, Inc.** complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively.  DoubleDutch, Inc. has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit privacyshield.gov.

  1. **What personal data do we collect from you?**

**Personal data you provide to us**

When using the Apps, you may provide us with personal data. Personal data includes all personally identifiable information (“PII”) and data that directly or indirectly identifies you such as your name, email address, phone number and location data. You control how much information you provide through the Apps. To use our Apps, you must provide an email and username, and you will set a password. If you did not submit this information yourself, we have received this information from the event organizer to invite you to use the Apps and to prepopulate certain fields in the Apps. An App Provider may request additional information about you beyond a user name and email address. It is up to you how much additional personal information you share with us, the event organizer, and the other attendees. When using the Apps you may choose to create social profiles that display your name, job title, company, links to your social profiles (Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn) and activity. In addition to the above, you can fill out an "About Me" text box to provide additional information about yourself, as well as contribute through posts, comments, surveys, messages, poll responses, and any other App-related functions or features that may be available to you. **Please do not include personal information in your posts, comments, surveys, messages, or poll responses.** If you are an event organizer, you may also provide us with conference agendas, customer lists, exhibitor lists, and other information.

**Personal data we collect through your use of our Apps or Website**

We collect limited personal data from you through your use of our Apps or Website. The only data we actively collect from you beyond that which you choose to provide are your IP address, browser software, operating system, and the time and date on which you visited the Apps or Website. In addition, we may also track your usage of the Apps for statistical and research purposes by means of cookies.

  2. **For what purpose do we use or process your personal data?**

We process your personal data for the following purposes:

  * Providing you with information about the event that you are attending;
  * Performing our services;
  * Enabling App features such as "check-ins", surveys/polls, messaging, channels, agenda sessions, exhibitors, recommendations, speakers and locations;
  * Prepopulating App fields such as conference agendas, attendee lists, speaker lists, exhibitor lists, and location information;
  * Showing your App contributions on the activity feeds in the event App;
  * For analytics and market research to perform or improve our services;
  * Sending emails or push notifications in relation to the event; and,
  * Processing complaints or customer service inquiries, handling disputes, performing audits and meeting statutory requirements.

We do not use automated decision-making when processing personal information. Please refer to the App Partner’s privacy policy for information regarding their use of personal information.

  3. **With whom do we share your personal data?**

We do not share your personal data with third parties, unless we have a good reason to do so.

**Event Organizers**

We share your information, posts, comments, surveys, messages, and polls with the event organizers or their authorized agents. In accordance with our legal obligations, we have agreed to safeguard the protection of your personal data in agreements with the event organizers. We recommend that you read and review the privacy policy of the event organizer carefully to ensure you are fully aware of all the purposes for which your data is being used by the event organizer or processed by us.

**Attendees**

Other users of the Apps may be able to see limited information such as your profile and contributions. Apart from the first and last name on your profile, we do not share your personal data with attendees. The only information that is visible to attendees is the information you decide to actively share on your profile or contribute to the Apps.

**Exhibitor**

We may share some of your information with exhibitors if you: click on "more information" on an exhibitor dashboard; allow the exhibitor to scan your contact information at the event; click consent on a pop-up box in the Apps; or click to consent to receive exhibitor offers tailored to your profile.

**External Partnerships**

We may provide personal information to our affiliates (<https://policies.google.com/privacy/key-terms#toc-terms-affiliates>) or other trusted businesses or persons to process that information for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other applicable confidentiality and security measures. For example, we might use data processors to handle complaints, to resolve customer service inquiries from you or event organizers, to facilitate internal support operations for DoubleDutch, to send newsletters or other event information on our or the event organizer’s behalf, or to share information with third parties in other similar cases if you have provided your consent to such data sharing. We will not sell to any third party the personal information or data that you provide to us.

**Payment Processors**

We use third-party payment processors to process payments for our registration App Partners. In connection with the processing of such payments, we do not retain any personally identifiable information or any financial information such as credit card numbers. Rather, all such information is provided directly to the third-party processor the App Partner selects, whose use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policy.

**Legal Requirements and Law Enforcement**

We will share personal information where we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request (<https://policies.google.com/privacy/example/legal-process>); detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of DoubleDutch, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**Other Third Parties**

As an extension to this Privacy Policy and if requested by a partner company for transfer of personal data outside the European Economic Area, we may enter into EU Standard Contractual Clauses to comply with our legal obligations.

**Corporate Organization**

In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar events, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  4. **Security of your personal information**

In accordance with the applicable laws and regulations, we have taken adequate technical and organizational measures to safeguard the security of your personal information. We store the personal information that we process on a secure database that is protected by technical access controls. We periodically review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

Please be advised that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable data, we make no guarantees or assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, access, or misuse and are not responsible in the event that such loss or misuse occurs.

  5. **What are your rights?**

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, DoubleDutch commits to resolving complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. Additionally, based on the Dutch Data Protection Act (Wet bescherming persoonsgegevens) and similar local laws that pertain to the countries in which our companies have nexus, you may request to review, change, or remove your personal data. European Union, Swiss, or other covered individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact DoubleDutch by email by including your full name and sending it to privacy@doubledutch.me.  We will contact you within thirty (30) business days after receipt of a request to review, change, or remove your personal data.

If the complaint cannot be resolved through DoubleDutch’s internal processes, it will be referred to Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc., (JAMS) under the JAMS International Mediation Rules, which are accessible on the JAMS website at [www.jamsadr.com/rules-international-rules](https://www.jamsadr.com/international-mediation-rules/).  JAMS mediation may also be commenced as provided for in the JAMS International Mediation Rules. You may also submit a claim directly to JAMS through the following site, which is maintained by JAMS: <https://www.jamsadr.com/international-arbitration-rules/>. Finally, you will also have the possibility to invoke binding arbitration under certain conditions.

The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.

DoubleDutch is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and the applicable EU or Swiss Supervisory Authority. In certain circumstances, the Privacy Shield Framework provides the right to invoke binding arbitration to resolve complaints not resolved by other means, as described in Annex I to the Privacy Shield Principles (<https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>). If applicable, under EU or Swiss law, You may lodge a complaint with our arbitration provider, JAMS, or the applicable Supervisory Authority.

If applicable, under EU law, You may: withdraw consent for processing your personal information at any time; object to or restrict processing; or request DoubleDutch to provide you a copy of your personal information, information about processing, or a correction or deletion of your personal information.

  6. **Cookies and similar technologies**

We use cookies and web beacons in our Apps and on our Website. A cookie is a small text file that is delivered with pages from the Apps or Website and which is stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or on your smartphone. Cookies have various functions, for example, a cookie can store your language preferences or password token. Web beacons are electronic files invisibly embedded on web pages or in email to permit the sender to track online movements of web users. Cookies and web beacons do not usually contain any information that could personally identify you.

At this time we do not respond to browser ‘do not track’ signals, as we await the development of industry standards for how such signals should be interpreted.

Appendix 1 lists the types of Cookies we use and their purpose.

You can turn off the use of cookies via the settings on your computer or your smartphone. Please note, turning off cookies can result in some functions of the website or Apps not working properly. You may directly opt-out from Google Analytics cookies by contacting Google.

  7. **Additional Information and Contacts**

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our services are directed to the general public. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age or have any reasonable grounds for believing that children under the age of 13 are accessing our Website or using our Apps or services. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, or if you wish to remove publicly available content, please contact us at privacy@doubledutch.me or the mailing address in this Privacy Policy.

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request to us in writing.

**Retention Period**

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. If required by law, as is the case to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will nullify such personal information by erasing it from our database.

**Limitations of Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in the Apps or services, or at an event or function supported by DoubleDutch technologies. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who may advertise through our Apps, and who may use technologies to serve ads or offer relevant information to you.

If you have questions about our use of your personal data, please contact us at:

DoubleDutch, Inc. and its Subsidiaries’

Data Protection Officer:

Kasper Jeppesen

Attn: Legal Department

44 Tehama Street, Suite 502

San Francisco, CA 94105 USA

privacy@doubledutch.me

| Please refer to the App Partner’s Privacy Policy for the App Partner contact information.  
---|---  
  
If you have questions about the event organizer’s use of your personal data, we recommend that you read and review the privacy policy of the event organizer and contact the event organizer if you still have questions.

**Appendix 1: Cookies and Purpose**

We use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your device for a set period of time or until you delete them). We use the following types of cookies for the purposes explained in this chart:

Cookie Type | Purpose  
---|---  
Essential operation | These cookies are necessary in order for you to move around the service as you request. It allows us to recognize what type of attendee, exhibitor, or other subscriber you are so that we can then accordingly provide services.  
Functional | These cookies allow us to use certain features of the service in accordance with the choices that you make. These cookies mean that if you continue to use the services or return to the services, we can then provide services tailored for you based on the choices you have made or asked us to hold like your username or your customizations.  
Performance and Analysis | We use performance cookies to help us provide a better user experience for you based on optimizing the services and constantly optimizing the features and performance. We may also obtain information from features that you open or access or click on. This information tells us about the effectiveness of certain features and helps ensure that the content and features we provide are optimized for your interests.  
Third party | We can allow our business partners to use cookies on or the service as indicated for the same purposes as we provide you with services, including gathering information about your online and in-App activities over time and across our services. We can also use service providers acting on our behalf to use cookies for the purposes described above.
